[{"id": "5fdffb241cf6db9ac4808cf5", "question": "What is the oldest city in India?", "answer": "Varanasi", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338926", "question": "Who is the father of the Hulkling?", "answer": "Captain Marvel", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "600243894be4723ccac22198", "question": "What was the name of the first book in Laura Ingalls Wilder\u2019s \"Little House\" series?", "answer": "\"Little House in the Big Woods\"", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113399e1", "question": "What is the last name of the brothers in the band AC/DC?", "answer": "Young", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5a9e92be7ccba3ffe45786bb", "question": "Mr. Mybug was only interested in sex with Flora in what book?", "answer": "Cold Comfort Farm", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339678", "question": "In the TV show \"The Simpsons\", who is Patty and Selma's favorite TV hero?", "answer": "MacGyver", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f8f", "question": "What actress earned an Oscar nomination for her first screen appearance in \"Gaslight\"?", "answer": "Angela Lansbury", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a09", "question": "Who played the first \"Tool Time Girl\" on the TV show \"Home Improvement\"?", "answer": "Pamela Anderson", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fdc1277469bb8041d07a07c", "question": "Vampires are typically known for turning into which animal?", "answer": "Bat", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a466", "question": "In what state would you find the Black Rock Desert?", "answer": "Nevada", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339381", "question": "What did Elwood trade for a microphone in the movie \"The Blues Brothers\"?", "answer": "A Cadillac", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe8b37701dd7bf43be5e7b0", "question": "A kindle is a group of what animals?", "answer": "Kittens", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f67", "question": "What does \"Alma mater\" translate to in English?", "answer": "Bountiful mother", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a29b", "question": "Which English director founded the Theatre Workshop?", "answer": "Joan Littlewood", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5a9e96237ccba3ffe45786e9", "question": "In Greek mythology, who did Athena turn into a spider?", "answer": "Arachne", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b175", "question": "What year was the state of California ceded to the US from Mexico?", "answer": "1848", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ffcfd749dc5ec6cd98a8324", "question": "What famous literary character offers this sage advice: \"Neither a borrower nor a lender be\"?", "answer": "Polonius (In\u00a0\"Hamlet\"\u00a0(Act I, Scene III),\u00a0he offers the sage advice to his son Laertes who is about to leave home.)", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b299", "question": "Who was the only slave ever known to have stayed in Thomas Jefferson's household?", "answer": "Sally Hemings", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ff0adf0e662d71a53650fb5", "question": "Who became famous for painting New Mexico landscapes from her Model A Ford?", "answer": "Georgia O\u2019Keeffe", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e12", "question": "What two \"Brokeback Mountain\" actors have siblings who are also award-winning actors?", "answer": "Jake Gyllenhaal and Randy Quaid", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe93ac66bd93ce3a4e5f69b", "question": "What is the scientific study of animal biology?", "answer": "Zoology", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f031133897a", "question": "In the book \"Animal Farm\", what boar originally encouraged the other animals to rebel against Farmer Jones?", "answer": "Old Major", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c97a", "question": "The North Star is also known as?", "answer": "Polaris", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c6d8", "question": "What element combines with sodium to make ordinary table salt?", "answer": "Chlorine", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339800", "question": "What label owns the rights to every Elvis recording ever made", "answer": "RCA", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b32c", "question": "Where did Queen Victoria and Prince Albert get married?", "answer": "St. James' Palace", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b21c", "question": "What city was Wild Bill Hickok killed in?", "answer": "Deadwood", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe735e8eec85e375820b255", "question": "What did John Wilkes Booth trip on as he jumped on the stage of Ford's Theater?", "answer": "Bunting", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ff9", "question": "In Greek mythology, who hired Daedalus to construct the Labyrinth?", "answer": "King Minos", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ae5a", "question": "Who was Germany's first female chancellor?", "answer": "Angela Merkel", "category": "history"}, {"id": "601217d863c99d48cd169aeb", "question": "What dog breed has a name that translates to \"little brushwood dog\"?", "answer": "Shiba Inu", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a7ea", "question": "Which US state is named after a King of England?", "answer": "Georgia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a8f6", "question": "Of the US states that border Mexico, which shares the shortest border?", "answer": "California", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b42d", "question": "What year did Alfred Hitchcock become a citizen of the United States?", "answer": "1955", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe4ec1406d333868d34d760", "question": "The name \"Australia\" was formally adopted in which year?", "answer": "1824", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe7c848877e98cb977789e1", "question": "Which country has hosted the Wife Carrying World Championships since the competition\u2019s founding in 1992?", "answer": "Finland", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b0b5", "question": "The March of Dimes was originally founded to help find a vaccine for what?", "answer": "Polio", "category": "history"}, {"id": "6010ca4c0775fa611bce67f6", "question": "What is another name for rubbing alcohol?", "answer": "Isopropyl alcohol -- It is a germicide that is effective against bacteria, viruses, and fungi.", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133991c", "question": "Who occupied the center square on the game show \u201cThe Hollywood Squares\u201d from 1998\u00ad to 2002?", "answer": "Whoopi Goldberg", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b2d9", "question": "What military legend was nicknamed \"Gentleman Johnny\"?", "answer": "John Burgoyne", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5a9e93d17ccba3ffe45786ca", "question": "What was Buddy Holly's real first name?", "answer": "Charles", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe8f82901dd7bf43be5e841", "question": "Gnosiophobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "Knowledge", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c8e2", "question": "Saanen, hongtong and toggenburg are all breeds of which animal?", "answer": "Goats", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a72a", "question": "Lake Pend Oreille is the largest lake in which US state?", "answer": "Idaho", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aaff", "question": "Thunder Bay is located in which country?", "answer": "Canada\u00a0", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe738e8eec85e375820b26a", "question": "Where is the USA's first ski town located?", "answer": "Woodstock, Vermont", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a6d3", "question": "Which New England state does not have any ocean coastline?", "answer": "Vermont", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a422", "question": "What is the capital of New Zealand?", "answer": "Wellington", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a4c6", "question": "Where is Mount Olympus?", "answer": "Greece", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a3b1", "question": "Which country contains Lake Assal, the lowest point on mainland Africa?", "answer": "Djibouti", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b4bf", "question": "Who was assassinated by her own bodyguards in 1984?", "answer": "Indira Gandhi", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339240", "question": "What George Michael song was banned by the BBC and re-edited three times for MTV?", "answer": "I Want Your Sex", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a6c3", "question": "Big Bend National Park protects what mountain range?", "answer": "Chisos Mountains", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c97c", "question": "What constellation is the North Star located in?", "answer": "Ursa Minor", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ae2b", "question": "Who led his troops to disaster at the Little Bighorn in 1876?", "answer": "George Custer", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fd96bc923c87fd04dd15e1e", "question": "Which sitting US President was first to travel by plane?", "answer": "Franklin D Roosevelt", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a111", "question": "What does the \"E\" stand for in Wile E. Coyote's name?", "answer": "Ethelbert", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59049d99cf93664eb10486af", "question": "The plane carrying what country\u2019s national rugby team crashed on Friday, October 13, 1972?", "answer": "Uruguay\u2019s", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a69", "question": "For what 1997 film did Kim Basinger win a Best Supporting Actress Oscar?", "answer": "L.A. Confidential", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339fef", "question": "What cartoon character is named for Princess Dala's diamond in a 1963 film?", "answer": "The Pink Panther", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b838", "question": "What 1960s invention was originally called the \"Pleasure Pit\"?", "answer": "Waterbed", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5a9e94cc7ccba3ffe45786d7", "question": "What year did the programming language \"COBOL\" first appear, before being standardized in 1968?", "answer": "1959", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a1f", "question": "From 1964 to 1975, who was the original host of the TV game show \"Jeopardy\"?", "answer": "Art Fleming", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a00e", "question": "Whose Atlantic recordings are collected in a set called \"Queen of Soul\"?", "answer": "Aretha Franklin", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be06", "question": "What sports term is also the name of the dimple at the bottom of a wine bottle?", "answer": "Punt", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c0f8", "question": "Who was the second Toronto Blue Jay player to lead the American league in home runs?", "answer": "Fred McGriff", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b590", "question": "What is by far the best known product by Victorinox?", "answer": "Swiss Army Knife", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5b7abb606490a8cc1a6e5296", "question": "How many flavors of quarks are there?", "answer": "6", "category": "science"}, {"id": "6015de83fe83fe1f2a824b6c", "question": "What actor was one of the most decorated American combat soldiers of World War II?", "answer": "Audie Murphy", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5a25ef236682715b82711cd4", "question": "What year did the Invasion of Normandy take place?", "answer": "1944", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe9f0cfff048f679a45aaa7", "question": "Tonitrophobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "Thunder", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fdc143b469bb8041d07a085", "question": "Which U.S. best-selling wine is often referred to as \"over-oaked\" and \"not food-friendly\"?", "answer": "Chardonnay", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5f3052145aa2bc17b61b2ac8", "question": "Chisinau is the capital of what country?", "answer": "Moldova", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "601b4c7c49076251badbead5", "question": "Which newspaper incorrectly reported Thomas E. Dewey defeated Harry S. Truman in the 1948 U.S. Presidential Election?", "answer": "Chicago Daily Tribune -- Now known as Chicago Tribune, it had once referred to Truman as a \"nincompoop\".", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338c2f", "question": "Who wrote \"How the Grinch Stole Christmas\"?", "answer": "Dr. Seuss", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "601b4c2749076251badbeace", "question": "How many U.S. Presidents fathered no children?", "answer": "Five -- George Washington, James Polk, Warren Harding, James Buchanan, and Andrew Jackson fathered no children.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "58d1178b4fea7fe947a2227a", "question": "What is the name for the study of fluids?", "answer": "Hydraulics", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5febb7957e83c707845b2131", "question": "The transition of a substance directly from the solid state to the gas state, without passing through the liquid state is called?", "answer": "Sublimation", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5feba93e7e83c707845b20d4", "question": "What is suspended from the ceiling of the American Natural History Museum?", "answer": "Blue whale", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fecca88ec223966ae8f889a", "question": "In American football, the area behind the line of scrimmage is known as what?", "answer": "The backfield", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133aef1", "question": "When did The Black Death reach London?", "answer": "1348", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113398a3", "question": "Who directed the movie \"The Passion of the Christ\"?", "answer": "Mel Gibson", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339399", "question": "How many brothers did Ryan lose in the movie \"Saving Private Ryan\"?", "answer": "Three", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c60c", "question": "Entomologists study what?", "answer": "Insects", "category": "science"}, {"id": "59cdb0dc65ff7d326b622a64", "question": "Who released the 1970's album entitled \"Pretzel Logic\"?", "answer": "Steely Dan", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5963724f967692ea851899be", "question": "A jellyfish is made up of 95% of what?", "answer": "Water", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5ff6706e52a821ff76ae8b21", "question": "What is a cartomancer?", "answer": "A fortune teller who uses cards", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ff513b4ff04d658268c92de", "question": "What naval battle between Mark Antony and Octavian is often said to mark the beginning of the Roman Empire?", "answer": "The\u00a0Battle of Actium", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391a7", "question": "Who played Mad Max Rockatansky?", "answer": "Mel Gibson", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d30", "question": "What novel is Aldous Huxley's fifth novel?", "answer": "A Brave New World", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a0db", "question": "Who composed the music for the opera \"The Tales of Hoffman\"?", "answer": "Jacques Offenbach", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59071e123745b36be73039e1", "question": "What was the name of the first US human spaceflight?", "answer": "Mercury-Redstone 3, aka Freedom 7", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac96", "question": "Who was Elizabeth I's father?", "answer": "Henry VIII", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fecc1b8ec223966ae8f886d", "question": "The three actors who starred as Magneto, Iron Man and Doctor Strange have all played what other character?", "answer": "Sherlock Holmes", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ab99b0d21a8909e5c332d27", "question": "In which film did Marlene Dietrich sing \"See What the Boys in the Back Room Will Have\"?", "answer": "Destry Rides Again", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c445", "question": "What fluid is stored in the gallbladder?", "answer": "Bile", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c4c4", "question": "What term for a rocket's propulsive force is calculated by multiplying its exhaust velocity by the burn rate of its fuel?", "answer": "Thrust", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe8eefc01dd7bf43be5e7ef", "question": "Roquefort, manchego, and feta cheese are produced from what animal's milk?", "answer": "Sheep", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339bd9", "question": "What year was Mark Wahlberg born?", "answer": "1971", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bded", "question": "What is the 3 letter code for O'Hare International Airport?", "answer": "ORD", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be3c", "question": "How many on-field players are there in a standard Australian rules football team?", "answer": "Eighteen", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5af25996b63e5727cf5a4850", "question": "Which Jamiroquai music video won a Grammy and 4 MTV Video Music Awards?", "answer": "Virtual Insanity", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ccb", "question": "What stadium hit do we owe to a pre-Civil War folk song and the Swedish dance band Rednex?", "answer": "Cotton Eye Joe", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113396e1", "question": "What TV show takes place in Pawnee, Indiana?", "answer": "Parks and Recreation", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c838", "question": "Bauxite ore is mined so it can be processed into what metal?", "answer": "Aluminum", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c72a", "question": "What constellation's Latin name translates as \"Smaller Bear\" or \"Little Bear\"?", "answer": "Ursa Minor", "category": "science"}, {"id": "6018bbedd96d05b23b281651", "question": "The Peloponnesian War was fought between Athens and which other ancient Greek state?", "answer": "Sparta", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b946", "question": "What is the only pasta to eat for good luck on New Years Day, according to Sicilian tradition?", "answer": "Lasagna", "category": "general"}, {"id": "60136f851381754895396377", "question": "What superhero uses a device called \"The Cosmic Treadmill\"?", "answer": "Flash -- The Cosmic Treadmill is used to help the Flash amplify his already considerable powers.", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c75a", "question": "What is another name for the disease known as Varicella?", "answer": "Chickenpox", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d8d", "question": "What original literary work was the movie \"Gettysburg\" based on?", "answer": "The Killer Angels", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c50f", "question": "What is the only fruit to have its seeds on the outside?", "answer": "Strawberry", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca50", "question": "Honeydew is a variety of what?", "answer": "Melon", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bea4", "question": "What do sumo wrestlers throw into the ring to purify it before each bout?", "answer": "Salt", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a6e5", "question": "What lake was created in the 1900s when the Colorado River broke through an embankment?", "answer": "Salton Sea", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "596dfb90cf3977a46e7ce44a", "question": "The average person has over 1,460 of what each year?", "answer": "Dreams", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe6a98120565ad31a57c805", "question": "Who founded the University of Virginia?", "answer": "Thomas Jefferson", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5c3e98a0ebfabb9c85d8a96d", "question": "What is the name for the creamy liver of lobster eaten as a delicacy?", "answer": "Tomalley", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fd81c58d0de9af39e9d4683", "question": "What were acorns used to create during the Civil War?", "answer": "Coffee", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ee3", "question": "By what professional name is comic book writer Stanley Martin Leiber better known?", "answer": "Stan Lee", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "6010ca1f0775fa611bce67f3", "question": "What Apple computer was named after Steve Jobs' daughter?", "answer": "Lisa", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b2e4", "question": "Where did two lanterns historically hang on the night of April 18, 1775?", "answer": "Boston's Old North Church", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fea3a63ff048f679a45ab2b", "question": "What does the human lacrimal gland produce?", "answer": "Tears", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338fe1", "question": "Who is Lois Lane's younger sister?", "answer": "Lucy Lane", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a2e0", "question": "What year did actor Arthur Stanley Jefferson die?", "answer": "1965", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b85", "question": "What is the name of the rabbit in the movie \"Bambi\"?", "answer": "Thumper", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59f9b7a7364247bf200fb874", "question": "Who had a hit in 1988 with the song \"I Get Weak\"?", "answer": "Belinda Carlisle", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca0d", "question": "Which island is the Dodo originally from?", "answer": "Mauritus", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fd9725723c87fd04dd15e52", "question": "In which country was the umbrella invented?", "answer": "China", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59636f8f967692ea851899b6", "question": "In what game do you have the greatest chance of landing on Illinois Avenue?", "answer": "Monopoly", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113390fa", "question": "Who wrote the 1991 novel \"The Deceiver\"?", "answer": "Frederick Forsyth", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b6a8", "question": "What gaming company originally publish the games \"Bejeweled\" and \"Peggle\"?", "answer": "PopCap", "category": "general"}, {"id": "593c4a60b8198b9a2b07795b", "question": "Who played the male lead role in the film \"Terminator Salvation\"?", "answer": "Sam Worthington", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c1d2", "question": "What bar is credited with debuting the Grasshopper cocktail?", "answer": "Tujague's", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fd669b1a5bfecdd737e087e", "question": "What is the ninth month of the Islamic calendar called?", "answer": "Ramadan", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fdab92a0b8cce1e6fda7053", "question": "The most popular car color in the USA for 2019 was which color?", "answer": "White", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58dba36d874c93a3298b213b", "question": "A male with more than two testicles is said to suffer from what disorder?", "answer": "Polyorchidism", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe65dc71f3c0ead6880d621", "question": "What did God place at the east of the Garden of Eden after he drove out Adam and Eve?", "answer": "Cherubims", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59e8021ede59ea584496fe95", "question": "What is a group of squirrels called?", "answer": "Dray or a scurry", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c360", "question": "Who famously said \"Dr. Livingstone, I presume?\" in 1872?", "answer": "H.M. Stanley", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa34", "question": "What is the capital of Italy?", "answer": "Rome", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113393e9", "question": "Who recorded \"The Fool on the Hill\" in 1968?", "answer": "The Beatles", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b46c", "question": "Which two individuals were the first to reach the summit of Mount Everest in 1953?", "answer": "Sir Edmund Hillary and Tenzing Norgay", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113399df", "question": "In the 1991 animated Disney film \"Beauty and the Beast\", what type of enchanted item is Chip?", "answer": "A teacup", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113390bd", "question": "What nationality is crime writer Colin Dexter?", "answer": "English", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "600cc46f6de0eb824d4052f3", "question": "Which African country was formerly known as Abyssinia?", "answer": "Ethiopia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113392f8", "question": "In the movie \"Pulp Fiction\", what is the name of the restaurant Mia brings Vincent to?", "answer": "Jack-Rabbit Slim's", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c8e3", "question": "What is the Latin word for the liquid produced by the Ficus Elastica?", "answer": "Latex", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339217", "question": "What Stealers Wheel hit is heard in the movie \"Reservoir Dogs\"?", "answer": "Stuck in the Middle with You", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d4e", "question": "What actress shaved her head for her role in the movie \"The Girl in the Kremlin\"?", "answer": "Natalie Darryl", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a775", "question": "What famous \"Bay\" is Jamaica's fourth largest city?", "answer": "Montego Bay", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113398b1", "question": "What song earned Natalie Cole and Nat King Cole a Grammy Award in 1991?", "answer": "Unforgettable", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133915e", "question": "Who directed \"2001: A Space Odyssey\"?", "answer": "Stanley Kubrik", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "592205cea4edfd43a087adea", "question": "Of which country did F.W. de Klerk become president in 1989?", "answer": "South Africa", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ffb59e05dad637d903c8816", "question": "What country is nicknamed the \"Land of a Thousand Smiles\"?", "answer": "Thailand", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339bfa", "question": "What movie is credited with popularizing the \"little black dress\"?", "answer": "Breakfast at Tiffany's", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa6b", "question": "What is the capital of the US state of North Carolina?", "answer": "Raleigh", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5ff6670252a821ff76ae8afb", "question": "May Day was banned in England during which century?", "answer": "For a few years in the mid 17th Century, the church abolished May Day due to its revelrous nature.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd50", "question": "The Fields Medal is an award given in what field?", "answer": "Mathematics", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b36f", "question": "James Hunt was disqualified after winning which Grand Prix?", "answer": "1976 British Grand Prix", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f1a", "question": "What author created Prydain?", "answer": "Lloyd Alexander", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b4a1", "question": "Which country hosted the first Winter Olympic Games?", "answer": "France", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a3cf", "question": "What area of the Atlantic is said to be responsible for the disappearance of ships and aircraft?", "answer": "Bermuda Triangle", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "6016009afe83fe1f2a824c56", "question": "What was the subject of the first color photograph?", "answer": "A tartan ribbon", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b6fa", "question": "What winter Olympic event combines cross-country skiing with rifle shooting?", "answer": "Biathlon", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b23b", "question": "What royal subject married Sarah Ferguson?", "answer": "Prince Andrew", "category": "history"}, {"id": "60121a4763c99d48cd169b02", "question": "According to myth, who rode the flying horse named Sleipnir?", "answer": "Sleipnir, known as the fastest horses, carried Odin the All-Father through the sky, over the seas, and across the lands.", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a1a3", "question": "Who plays Pacey Witter on the TV show \"Dawson's Creek\"?", "answer": "Joshua Jackson", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a4d", "question": "Natty Bumppo was the creation of which author?", "answer": "James Fenimore Cooper", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133cad2", "question": "What is nephology the study of?", "answer": "Clouds", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a814", "question": "In what county is Chicago, Illinois located?", "answer": "Cook County", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac7b", "question": "Who became prime minister of Cuba in 1959?", "answer": "Fidel Castro", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59cdb56e65ff7d326b622a92", "question": "This is the Southeast Asian method of dying fabric using wax to create designs?", "answer": "Batik", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5a899ca560d398dc9cf7a6a8", "question": "In Greek mythology, who are Hestia's six siblings?", "answer": "Demeter, Hera, Hades, Zeus, Poseidon, Chiron", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339cfd", "question": "In which movie did Veronica Lake portray a witch?", "answer": "I Married a Witch", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a294", "question": "What band eventually evolved into the Bee Gees?", "answer": "The Rattlesnakes", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe8acb601dd7bf43be5e770", "question": "Stollen is a traditional fruit-and-nut holiday bread from which country?", "answer": "Germany", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b8c7", "question": "In which decade was the Rubik's Cube invented?", "answer": "1970s", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339659", "question": "In the TV show \"The Simpsons\", what is the name of Snake's car?", "answer": "Li'l Bandit", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5a25f2b06682715b82711cec", "question": "Margarita Carmen Cansino became famous as who?", "answer": "Rita Hayworth", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339bba", "question": "For how many years were Madonna and Sean Penn married?", "answer": "4", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58b8d7312b42d4a3561a9f0b", "question": "Prior to joining the revived \u201cTop Gear\u201d TV series in 2003, what year did James May co-host the original \u201cTop Gear\u201d series?", "answer": "1999", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fecc0f8ec223966ae8f8862", "question": "Why were the Boston Red Sox said to be \"cursed\" between 1918 and 2004?", "answer": "For trading Babe Ruth", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c44c", "question": "How many chromosomes does a goat have?", "answer": "60", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f51", "question": "\"Girls with a Pearl Earring\" is one of only thirty-five extant works of what Dutch painter?", "answer": "Jan Vermeer", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b072", "question": "Approximately how long did the Pony Express run?", "answer": "18 months", "category": "history"}, {"id": "600f71c1a9e54d890926f6e5", "question": "Texas is home to the longest-running what?", "answer": "State fair -- Lasting 24 days, the Texas State Fair is one of Dallas's most popular events.", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "600b87e51d8c1817608d53eb", "question": "What is the Latin word for \"seasickness\", now commonly used to describe any feeling of sickness?", "answer": "Nausea", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fdc0c3d469bb8041d07a04f", "question": "Who is considered \"The Father of Modern French Cooking\"?", "answer": "August Escoffier", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339fe8", "question": "What children's TV character lived in the Treasure House?", "answer": "Captain Kangaroo", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "601b4c3b49076251badbead0", "question": "Which First Lady was the first to graduate college?", "answer": "Lucy Hayes -- The wife of President Rutherford B. Hayes, she received her degree from Wesleyan Female College at the age of 18.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fea3477ff048f679a45aaf8", "question": "What is the bone diseases that literally translates to \"porous bones\"?", "answer": "Osteoporosis", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133953b", "question": "Who appeared on the first cover of TV Guide?", "answer": "Lucille Ball", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5b6991b5e762b54eb9be941c", "question": "Into how many sectors is the standard dartboard divided into?", "answer": "20", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fffa58973838c5c8a417f26", "question": "What insects are sometimes called devil\u2019s darning needles?", "answer": "Dragonfly (They\u2019ve also been called darners and devil\u2019s arrows.)", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a720", "question": "Which city is home to the South-of-Market district?", "answer": "San Francisco", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "59ded371ea2747c8aff16d48", "question": "What is the name of the cloud-riding, glasses-wearing koopa in the Super Mario Bros. series?", "answer": "Lakitu", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe73433eec85e375820b230", "question": "Who was the overall commander of the Pacific Fleet during World War II?", "answer": "Admiral Chester Nimitz", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b72c", "question": "What country does not tolerate outdoor Christmas lights?", "answer": "Saudi Arabia", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58d470b0f8e329de4f877894", "question": "Who was the NBA's most valuable player in 1976, 1977 and 1980?", "answer": "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339424", "question": "Which James Bond actor also appeared in the movie \"Lara Croft: Tomb Raider\"?", "answer": "Daniel Craig", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bb7f", "question": "Who was the losing coach in the first Super Bowl, played January 15, 1967?", "answer": "Hank Stram", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe7caee877e98cb97778a0f", "question": "Which Arab country's flag has a green cedar tree in the center?", "answer": "Lebanon", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5ffa3913c73aa70ea0b70ad7", "question": "Which settlers added an \"r\" to Arkansas?", "answer": "French (They were told by natives from an Illinois tribe that people in the area now called Arkansas were called \"Akansa\".)", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a087", "question": "Where are Rocket J. Squirrel and Bullwinkle Moose from?", "answer": "Frostbite Falls", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5c90d15d52800b05cac20f11", "question": "Who is the only actor/actress to be nominated for an Oscar for their role in the original Star Wars trilogy?", "answer": "Sir Alec Guinness", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391a0", "question": "What movie starred Johnny Depp as Willy Wonka?", "answer": "Charlie and the Chocolate Factory", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ff25bff31a458464a93c47c", "question": "What dish do the Japanese traditionally eat on New Year\u2019s Eve?", "answer": "Buckwheat noodles", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a894", "question": "What city is home to the Oriental Pearl Tower?", "answer": "Shanghai", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5ffa573cc73aa70ea0b70b33", "question": "Which is the only U.S. state whose motto is in French?", "answer": "Minnesota's motto is \u00a0\"L'etoile du Nord,\" which in English is \"Star of the North.\"", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b0d8", "question": "In what year did Michelangelo finish painting the ceiling of the Sistine Chapel?", "answer": "1512", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fd2d2a92596a59cbdfbd391", "question": "Equity State is the official nickname of which state?", "answer": "Wyoming", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338883", "question": "Who wrote Around the World in Eighty Days?", "answer": "Jules Verne", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a095", "question": "What was the name of Punky Brewster's dog?", "answer": "Brandon", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b878", "question": "What color does the bride commonly wear in China?", "answer": "Red", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a092", "question": "Who sang \"That's Alright Mama\"?", "answer": "Elvis Presley", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a79", "question": "What ethologist told the story of Elsa the lioness in the book \"Born Free\"?", "answer": "Joy Adamson", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113389d2", "question": "Which English spa city, the setting for many of her novels, boasts the Jane Austen Center?", "answer": "Bath", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c4d4", "question": "The fruit of the rose plant shares its name with what part of the body?", "answer": "The hips", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113394e3", "question": "What did Harry Stone wear under his judge's robes on the TV show \"Night Court\"?", "answer": "Blue jeans", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c70a", "question": "What element's atomic symbol is \"Co\"?", "answer": "Cobalt", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c0ab", "question": "What kind of a head does a Hieracosphinx possess?", "answer": "Hawk", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe6a7f720565ad31a57c7f1", "question": "What President\u2019s fondness for pork rinds made sales of the snack boom?", "answer": "George H. W. Bush", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338c77", "question": "Who wrote the 1955 controversial novel \"Lolita\"?", "answer": "Vladamir Nabokov", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "59cdb01b65ff7d326b622a60", "question": "In which continent would you find the Atlas Mountains?", "answer": "Africa", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a805", "question": "What is the name of the Canadian territory that shares a land border with Alaska?", "answer": "Yukon Territory", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "59008e77cf842fa4c4ba96b2", "question": "What two parties fought in the \"Battle of Jutland\"?", "answer": "United Kingdom and Germany", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c7d2", "question": "What is a whale's leap out of the water called?", "answer": "Breaching", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe0e470fcbed638185eaa28", "question": "Which Italian city is considered the birthplace of modern gelato?", "answer": "Florence", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be42", "question": "What sports team used the Swinging Friar as its team emblem until 1984?", "answer": "The San Diego Padres", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338908", "question": "How many spikes are there on the The Statue of Liberty's crown?", "answer": "Seven", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "594d08661a1c922dd1ac64c3", "question": "Hashimoto's disease is the malfunctioning of which gland?", "answer": "Thyroid", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c03a", "question": "Where is the Popliteal Fossa located?", "answer": "Back of the knee", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59a1eda012f2a7826b9b8734", "question": "In the film industry, what is the primary job of the \"Foley Artist\"?", "answer": "To add sound effects", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ad96", "question": "Ferdinand Marcos and Corazon Aquino have both been Presidents of which country?", "answer": "Philippines", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113390a6", "question": "Who wrote the opera \"Madama Butterfly\"?", "answer": "Giacomo Puccini", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fea42e7ff048f679a45ab7c", "question": "What body part does a butterfly use for tasting?", "answer": "Hind feet", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a121", "question": "For which movie did director John Schlesinger receive an Oscar in 1970?", "answer": "Midnight Cowboy", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b316", "question": "On April 11, 1990, California Angel Mike Witt combined with which starter to pitch a no-hit victory?", "answer": "Mark Langston", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc46", "question": "What year did professional tennis player, Andre Agassi, retire from tennis in?", "answer": "2006", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133921e", "question": "What does the \"L\" stand for in Samuel L. Jackson?", "answer": "Leroy", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a065", "question": "According to the song what did my true love give to me on the fifth day of Christmas?", "answer": "Five gold rings", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5be581825415ba52ed6f0ac2", "question": "Who is credited with building the first full-scale working steam locomotive?", "answer": "Richard Trevithick", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5febb17a7e83c707845b210d", "question": "What are the fuzzy ends of a dandelion called?", "answer": "Seed Heads", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c7a2", "question": "What nationality was inventor Alexander Graham Bell?", "answer": "Scottish", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a2c0", "question": "Who played the role of Kenneth Parcell on the TV show \"30 Rock\"?", "answer": "Jack McBrayer", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa1f", "question": "What is the capital of Poland?", "answer": "Warsaw", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339db0", "question": "What is the name of the American musician best known as the lead singer of the rock band Nirvana?", "answer": "Kurt Cobain", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c5cc", "question": "What is the name given to the largest number ever used in a mathematical proof?", "answer": "Graham's Number", "category": "science"}, {"id": "6016008ffe83fe1f2a824c55", "question": "Who took the very first photograph in the world?", "answer": "Nic\u00e9phore Ni\u00e9pce took the first known photograph, \"View from the Window at Le Gras\", between 1826 and 1827.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113394c4", "question": "Which star of \"Cheers\" also starred in the TV show \"Veronica's Closet\"?", "answer": "Kirstie Alley", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113396a9", "question": "Which two friends won Oscars for their screenplay of the 1997 movie \"Good Will Hunting\"?", "answer": "Ben Affleck and Matt Damon", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338c85", "question": "What was the name of Tom Sawyer\u2019s aunt with whom he lived?", "answer": "Polly", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ff0b153e662d71a53650fd0", "question": "Who founded Dumbledore's Army?", "answer": "Hermione Granger", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ffa5289c73aa70ea0b70b1b", "question": "Which country serves as the home of the largest farm in the world?", "answer": "The Mudanjiang City Mega Farm is located in China and takes up almost 23 million acres.", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ae86", "question": "What fort did Benedict Arnold promise to surrender to the British, in return for money?", "answer": "West Point", "category": "history"}]